<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!--application name-->
    <string name="app_name">AdvancedRTM Install</string>
	<string name="launch_name">GoRTM</string>
	
	
	<string name="about">AdvancedRTM and GoRTM are copyright protected by Retro Modder 2019\n\nWhat is AdvancedRTM ?\nAdvanced RTM is an application that allows you to turn your Android device into a Real Time Modding Tool for PlayStation3 Consoles, You can edit in-game memory to enable cheats etc.\n\nCopyright © 2019 AdvancedRTM &amp; GoRTM. All Rights Reserved.\n\nTHIS SOFTWARE OR ANY PORTION THEREOF MAY NOT BE REPRODUCED, MODIFIED OR USED IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER WITHOUT THE EXPRESS WRITTEN PERMISSION FROM THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDER\'S.\n\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \"AS IS\", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.\n\nThis App Used the following resources to be built,\n\n• com.android.support:support-v4\n• com.android.support:appcompat-v7\n• com.android.support:design\n• org.jsoup:jsoup\n\nJsoup,\nJsoup is a licenced source code that can be used to interact with web documents, it has been used to communicate with WebMan Mod on your PS3 Console, License information can be found on their website.\n\nApp Support Libraries,\nThis app also uses Support libraries provided by Android for higher device compatibility, License information can be found on their website.\n</string>
	<string name="licence">AdvancedRTM License,\nAdvancedRTM called ( GoRTM ) is licensed under the Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivatives 4.0 International CC License found at https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/\n\nUnder the license, You are free to:\n• Share — copy and redistribute the material in any medium or format\nThe licensor cannot revoke these freedoms as long as you follow the license terms.\nUnder the following terms:\n\n• Attribution — You must give appropriate credit, provide a link to the license, and indicate if changes were made. You may do so in any reasonable manner, but not in any way that suggests the licensor endorses you or your use.\n• NonCommercial — You may not use the material for commercial purposes.\n• NoDerivatives — If you remix, transform, or build upon the material, you may not distribute the modified material.\n• No additional restrictions — You may not apply legal terms or technological measures that legally restrict others from doing anything the license permits.\n\nDisclaimer,\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \"AS IS\", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.\n\nLibraries License information,\n\nJsoup License,\nThe jsoup code-base (including source and compiled packages) are distributed under the open source MIT license as described below.\n\nThe MIT License\nCopyright © 2009 - 2019 Jonathan Hedley (jonathan@hedley.net)\nPermission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the \"Software\"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:\nThe above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \"AS IS\", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.\n\nAndroid Support Libraries License,\nThe Android Support Lib\'s are distributed under the Apache License version 2.0.\nCopyright (C) 2011 The Android Open Source Project\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\")\nyou may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\nYou may obtain a copy of the License at http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
	<string name="drawer_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="drawer_visibility">@string/drawer_content_on</string>
    <string name="drawer_content_on">0</string>
    <string name="drawer_content_off">2</string>

	<string-array name="list_array_example">
		<item>10/6/10 - Normal Speed</item> 
		<item>9/6/10 - Battery Saver</item> 
	</string-array> 
	
</resources>
